Soviet Union Unregistered Baptists Subject Files, Inclusive: 1948-2011, undated, Bulk: 1960-1989
Baylor University, The Keston Center for Religion, Politics, and Society
- Samizdat, 1961-1987, 2011, undated; 2
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 64: Extra copies, translated documents, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 65, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 65: Extra copies, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 66, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 67, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 68, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 69, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 70, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 70: Extra copies, translated documents, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 71, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 71: Extra copies, translated documents, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 72, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 72: Extra copies, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 73, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 73: Extra copy, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 74, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 74: Extra copy, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 75, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 75: Extra copies, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 76, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 76: Extra copy, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 77, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 77: Extra copy, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 78, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 79, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 80, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 81, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 82, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 84, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 85, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 86, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 87, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 88, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 89, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 90, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 91, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 92, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 93, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 94, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 95, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 96, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 97, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 98 (9), 1981 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 99 (10), 1981 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 100 (11), 1981 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 101 (1), 1982 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 102 (2), 1982 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 103 (3): Note, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 104 (4), 1982 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 105, 1982 May (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 106, 1982 June (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 107 (7), 1982 July (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 108 (8), 1982 August (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 109 (9), 1982 September-October (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 110, 1982 November-December (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 111, 1983 January (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 111: English summary, 1983 January (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 112, 1983 February (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 113, 1983 March-April (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 113, 1983 March-April (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 114, 1983 May-June (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 115, 1983 July-August (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 115: English summary, 1983 July-August (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 116, 1983 September-October (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 116: English summary, 1983 September-October (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 117, 1983 November (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 117: English summary, 1983 November (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 118, 1983 December (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 118: English summary, 1983 December (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 119, 1984 January-February (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 119: English summary, 1984 January-February (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 120, 1984 March (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 120: Extra copy, English summary, 1984 March (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 121, 1984 April-May (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 121: English summary, 1984 April-May (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 122, 1984 June-July (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 122: English summary, 1984 June-July (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 123, 1984 August-September (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 124, 1984 October-November (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 125, 1984 December (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 126, 1985 January (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 127, 1985 February (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 128, 1985 March-April (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 129, 1985 May (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 130, 1985 June (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 131, 1985 July-August (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 132, 1985 September-October (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 133, 1985 November-December (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 134, 1986 January-April (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 135, 1986 May-June-July (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 136, 1986 August-September (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 137, 1986 October-November (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 138, 1986 December (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 139, 1987 January-February (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 140, 1987 March-April (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 141, 1987 May-June-July (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 1, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 1: Extra copy, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, Nos. 1-3, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 1 (9), 1965 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 1 (9): Extra copy, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, Nos. 1-4: Notes, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 1 (13), 1966 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 1 (13): Extra copies, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 1 (17), 1967 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 1 (17): Extra copy, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 3 (19), 1967 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 3 (19): Extra copy, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 4 (20), 1967 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 1 (21), 1968 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 3 (23), 1968 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, Nos. 1-4: Notes, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia: Notes, 1969-1972 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 4 (32), 1970 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 1 (37), 1972 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 2 (38), 1972 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 2 (38): Extra copy, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 4, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 1, 3, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 1-2 (45-46), 1974 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 1-2 (45-46), 1974 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 4 (48), 1974 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 1-2 (49-50), 1975 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik spaseniia, No. 3-4 (51-52), 1975 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 1 (53), 1976 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 1 (53): Extra copy, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 1 (53): Extra copy, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 1 (53): English translation of Vins' letter to Gennagii Kriuchkov, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 2 (54), 1976 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 2 (54): Extra copy, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 3-4 (55-56), 1976 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 3-4 (55-56), 1976 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 1 (57), 1977 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 1 (57): Extra copy, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 1 (57): Poems by Georgii Vins, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 2-3 (58-59), 1977 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 2-3 (58-59): Extra copy, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 4 (60), 1977 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 1 (61), 1977 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 2-3 (62-63), 1978 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 2-3 (62-63), 1978 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 4 (64), 1978 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 1 (65), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 2 (66), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 3 (67), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 4 (68), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 1 (69), 1980 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 2 (70), 1980 (Box 30, Folder 25)